If you don't want to live in the village
Renting a place in town is fine too
No, no, no
We're not renting
We don't want to be a burden
We'll just sleep at the farm
We can sleep anywhere
We can also help you with the work
We can't be freeloaders
Yeah
I heard all your workers left
You must be short on hands
Your dad and I are still fit
We can help you out
I'll leave Mom and Dad with you
Daniel
Why are you running so fast
I'm sorry
For causing you trouble
It's fine
I was just worrying about having no workers
And being overwhelmed with work these days
Then Mom and Dad came just in time
This is definitely not that simple
Let's see
What kind of tricks you're playing this time
Sweetie
I heard that Lewes
Created a secret recipe
That makes the forest frogs grow super fast
And a big boss
Wants to buy it at a high price
Yeah
But
Lewes didn't sell it
Do you know the recipe
Of course